<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>usefullog.com</title>
    <link>http://usefullog.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on usefullog.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 22:36:56 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://usefullog.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>San Diego</title>
      <link>http://usefullog.com/posts/2023-06-san-diego/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 22:36:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usefullog.com/posts/2023-06-san-diego/</guid>
      <description>Birthplace of California Before I visited this city, I have been hearing good thing about San Diego. The perfect weather, good food, and fun activities. One thing I did not know before my trip, is that it is also an old city. In fact, the Old Town San Diego is referred to as the &amp;ldquo;birthplace&amp;rdquo; of California. The yard in La Casa de Estudillo, the iconic building in the old town plaza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan</title>
      <link>http://usefullog.com/posts/2023-05-taiwan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usefullog.com/posts/2023-05-taiwan/</guid>
      <description>Coffee on top of Tapei 101 My friend introduced me to Simple Kaffa in Taipei. The brand was established by Wu after he won the World Barista Championship in 2016. Simple Kaffa offers gourmet coffee beans from rare source in small batches. Most interestingly, it serves coffee that is grown locally in Taiwan.
Simple Kaffa has multiple locations, and this one - Simple Kaffa Sola - is on the 88th floor of Taipei 101.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alaska</title>
      <link>http://usefullog.com/posts/2023-04-04-alaska/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usefullog.com/posts/2023-04-04-alaska/</guid>
      <description>Matanuska Glacier A guided tour and the hosts take you to and from the glacier with a snowmobile-driven sled. In winter you can walk on icy surface when Matanuska Glacier is frozen. I brought trekking poles but actually it was not needed because they give ice cleats to everyone. You can hear the cracking sound from the glacier movement when the surrounding is quite. You can also see that huge ice blocks being pushed upwards by the glacier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illinois</title>
      <link>http://usefullog.com/posts/2023-03-illinois/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usefullog.com/posts/2023-03-illinois/</guid>
      <description>With the advance of phone camera technology, anyone can easily take good quality pictures. I have been posting photos on Instagram for years but it gets less and less frequent recently. One drawback of posting on the social media site is that the service can become obsolete one day, eventually. Posting on website may not be as easy as posting on Instagram, but I can try. Maybe there is a way to make it easier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://usefullog.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://usefullog.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It is only by selection, by elimination, by emphasis that we get at the real meaning of things. &amp;ndash; Georgia O&amp;rsquo;Keeffe&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
